var questionsObj = {
  quizName : "Demo Quiz IV",
  quizTags : ["GK"],
  startTime : 1540933200000,
  questionCount : 10,
  questions: [
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 16',
      question: 'Which country is known as the `Sugar Bowl of the World`?',
      options: {
        option1: 'Cuba',
        option2: 'Brazil',
        option3: 'Mexico',
        option4: 'Algeria'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Cuba'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 17',
      question: 'The first Woman Chief Minister of an Indian State is ________',
      options: {
        option1: 'Sarojini Naidu',
        option2: 'Sucheta Kripalani',
        option3: 'Indira Gandhi',
        option4: 'Rajkumari Amrita Kaur'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Sucheta Kripalani'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 18',
      question: 'Which of these organelles is also called `The Powerhouse of the cell`? ',
      options: {
        option1: 'Lymosomes',
        option2: 'Mitochondria',
        option3: 'Chloroplast',
        option4: 'Golgi bodies'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Mitochondria'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 19',
      question: 'Which country does the Equator NOT pass through?',
      options: {
        option1: 'Brazil',
        option2: 'Equador',
        option3: 'Maldives',
        option4: 'Nigeria'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Nigeria'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 20',
      question: 'Which of the following car brands has the slogan "There is no substitute"? ',
      options: {
        option1: 'Aston Martin',
        option2: 'Ferrari',
        option3: 'BMW',
        option4: 'Porche'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Porche'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 16',
      question: 'Complete the sequence: 45, 47, 41, 43, 37, ___',
      options: {
        option1: '31',
        option2: '39',
        option3: '35',
        option4: '33'
      },
      correctAnswer: '39'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 17',
      question: '37235 + 53761 ',
      options: {
        option1: '90,994',
        option2: '55,076',
        option3: '90,996',
        option4: '49,546'
      },
      correctAnswer: '90,996'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 18',
      question: 'What is the minimum number of times you have to rotate the dice in one direction to come back to the same number?',
      options: {
        option1: '2',
        option2: '4',
        option3: '6',
        option4: '8'
      },
      correctAnswer: '4'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 19',
      question: 'What word out of these will come last in a dictionary : Inhibition, International, Incision, Inherent, Insomnia, Incorrect, Internal',
      options: {
        option1: 'Internal',
        option2: 'International',
        option3: 'Insomnia',
        option4: 'None of the above'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'International'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 20',
      question: 'If you are my wife\'s only husband\'s father, Who am I to you?',
      options: {
        option1: 'Father',
        option2: 'Brother',
        option3: 'Son',
        option4: 'Uncle'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Son'
    }
  ]}

  module.exports.quizQuestions = questionsObj;